A Aman Ullah

Frontend Developer

Since 2016

5+ Years of of React Experience. Skilled in Javascript, TypeScript, Nextjs, Advanced & Pixel Perfect UI Development and other frontend technologies. Currently Focused on frontend, and looking forward to developing my career as Fullstack Developer.

EXPERIENCE

ShareTrip LTD

2018 — Present (Dhaka) | Frontend Engineer (Lead)

- Built 5 iteration of SEO friendly Flight, Hotel, Visa,
 Holiday, Tour, Transfer's Services for the web platform.
- Enriched b2b platform.Currently Working on a new iteration of B2C web platfrom from scratch with Nextjs & Tyescript for better User and Developer experience.
- Leading the frontend team.

Rasuta Energy LTD

2020 — 2021 (UK - Remote) | Software Engineer

- Built React APP for Displaying London Air Forecast in Google Maps.
- > Developed Mobile Apps by flutter.
- > Also Built REST API Using Nestjs.

Pharma71

March 2018 — August 2018 (Dhaka) | Software Engineer

- > Built Pharma71 R&D Mobile app with React Native.
- Also written Reactjs/Redux and the markup for other applications.

Beatnik

February 2017 — March 2018 (Dhaka) | Front End Developer

- Created website and services for high valued local clients.
- Got my hand dirty with vanila Javascript on small to enterprise level projects.
- > Improved Performace and Usability of the websites.

EDUCATION

Victoria University of Bangladesh

2009 - 2014 | BA in English

CONTACT

linkedin.com/in/amanullah8225 ¬ iamanullah.com ¬ github.com/amanix007 ¬ amanullah8225@gmail.com ¬ (+88) 016 80 298 225 ¬ Dhaka, Bangladesh

SKILLS

JavaScript



Other

HTML	CSS	RES	ГАРІ	Pixel Perfe	ect UI Design
Git	React Native		Dart	Flutter	

PROJECTS

www.sharetrip.net **↗**

Since 2018 | Nextjs, React, TypeScript, Context API, MobX, Jest, RTL

Airpot Ag ↗

2020 - 2021 | JavaScript | React | NestJS | Mobx | Dart | Flutter

UK Based Air Pollution Dashboard for web and android.

ShareTrip Blog **₹**

2020 | JavaScript NextJS TypeScript ContextAPI Jest RTL

Covid Corpus ↗

2020 - 2021| JavaScript, React, ContextAPI, UI Global Compilation of all ongoing research on COVID-19 .

Pagebulb

2019 - 2020| JavaScript React NodeJS TypeScript ExpressJS REST API

Built an HTML Page Builder from scratch.

Ticketchai.com (Flight Booking Platform.)

2019 - 2020 | JavaScript React Redux React-Native AntD